

I pay great attention to code quality, software architecture, and team work. Strong analytical skills and a broad range of computer expertise that give me a good understanding and knowledge of analysis, design, coding, testing and deployment. I love new challenges and learning new skills. I consider myself an open and dynamic person. I'm always open to new opportunities and ways of expanding my knowledge. I want to be a part of the development of our future.

Fullstack Software Engineer

Einbecker Str. 78 10315 Berlin

0157 345 89750

sia.qnbr@gmail.com

Website:

http://codewithsia.com

Github:

https://github.com/SiaQnbr

Stackoverflow:

https://stackoverflow.com/users/1404642/siavash

Marital Status: Married

Date of Birth: 31.07.1988

Languages:

- English (Fluent)
- Persian (Native)
- German (Learning A1)

Education

- BSc in Software Engineering
 Mazandaran University of Science and Technology, July 2012
- AD in Software Engineering Azad University of Ghaemshahr, July 2009

Experiences

Senior Full-Stack Engineer
SON Group Corporation Group

Feb. 2017 – Jan. 2020 (3 Years)

SON is a Data-Science company. We developed BI applications for The Financial Ministry of Iran, Iranian Social Affairs Organization, and some of the other important enterprise customers.

One of the fundamental steps for each BI system is collecting data. I developed an application to let users enter their financial data. This application was a spreadsheet app like Google Sheet with additional custom language that allows end-users to design their financial forms without programming knowledge. It was based on Reactjs, Redux, Nodejs, and Expressjs.

Senior Software Engineer Soniran Itd.

Nov. 2015 – Jan. 2017 (1 Year and 1 Month)

Soniran ltd. was a national consortium between some financial companies.

- I was responsible for developing a web application for a discounting system based on debit cards. I helped design and build new microservices and increase test coverage of existing code.
- I also developed an E-Wallet and Credit System based on each user transaction and their dashboards. (with Reactjs, Redux)
 Notable Achievements: Reacts, Redux, Nodejs, Expressjs, Microservices, Kafka, PostgreSQL, Jest, Git, Design Patterns

Software Engineer Saman International Analysts

April 2012 - August 2015
April 2012 - August 2015
(3 Years and 4 Months)

Saman Co is a Banking Solution Company. I started my professional career as a C# Developer in an agile-based team at Saman company. We developed a CORE-Banking system. Our system has been launched into 1400 branches of Keshavarzi Bank. I had worked as many different roles and worked with various technologies, during these three years, such as:

- I developed an app based on ISO-8553 (Financial transaction card originated interchange messaging)
- I designed and developed an automatic and manageable Updating system as an independent feature for our CORE-Banking App.
- I was in charge of implementing banking logics like deposit, withdraw, transfer and etc. in our banking application.

Notable Achievements: Banking Logic, ASP.NET, WebForm, C#, Windows Services, WinForm, JavaScript, Html, CSS, JQuery, Reflection, Generics, SQL Server, DB2, PowerShell Scripting, T-SQL, OOP, Microsoft IIS, Telerik, Microsoft TFS

Skills

- Reactis, Redux, Redux-Thunk
- Nodejs, Expressjs
- REST API, Web Socket, GraphQL, RabbitMQ, Kafka, OpenAPI
- Javascript, ES6 & ES7, Typescript
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- · WebPack, Babel
- AWS, Lambada, Cloud9, Elastic BeansTalk, ECR, CodeCommit
- Docker, Kubernetes, CI/CD, PM2, Git, GitLab, Github, Eslint,
- HTML, CSS, SASS, PostCSS, Flexbox, UI/UX
- Material, Bootstrap, i18n, Lodash, Moment, Axois, HandleBars
- Enzyme, Jest, End-to-End Testing, Integration Testing, TDD
- MVC, OOP, AOP, Functional, SOLID,
- Design Patterns, Micro-service, Monolith
- · Agile, Scrum, Jira, Linux, Ubuntu

Certificates

- Git Starter course, Udemy | ID: UC-597NOQ46 | June 2019
- CSS Fundamentals course, Solo-learn | ID: #1023-14416357 | June 2019
- JavaScript Tutorial course, Solo-learn | ID: #1024-14416357 | June 2019
- HTML Fundamentals course, Solo-learn | ID: #1014-14416357 | May 2019
- Microsoft ASP.NET Core, Microsoft Virtual Academy | September 2018
- Robotics Workshop, Payame Noor University | PNU / December 2011
- Future of the Robots Workshop, PNU | December 2011
- 3Ds MAX Workshop Full Course, IAU University | December 2011
- ITEX 2008, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysian Invention and Design Society | May 2008
- Advanced VB6, Technical & Vocational Training | ID: 1876068/79000092 | May 2006
- CompTIA A+, Tehran Institute of Technology | Cert-id: 112-3855 | 16104 | January 2006

Patents

 Intelligent Anti Earthquake Bed for Patients At hospital, Intellectual Property Organization/ REGCode: 014253 / 854 / December 2011

Publications

 Modeling and simulation of traffic lights and controller unit systems by colored Petri net, Academic Journals | December 2011 | ISSN: 1992-1950 / DOI:10.5897/IJPS11.968

Hobbies

- Playing Guitar
- Coding as Hobby (I'm working on some little opensource project)
- Board Games
- Cooking

References available on request.